Courtney Engel

INTERN - Museum at Fashion Institute of Technology

Philadelphia, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Courtney-Engel/11c5ed456948d8c7

Highly motivated professional with experience in all facets of the museum industry: programing, exhibition, deaccessioning, collection management, education, fashion history. Well organized, team player with excellent communications and interpersonal skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

INTERN

Museum at Fashion Institute of Technology - 2016 to Present

- Designing a promotional packet for all winter events
- Researching and cumulating museum programming grants
- Organizing guest list for each event
- Co-facilitator of the first ever kindergarten school program

GRADUATE INTERN

Robert - 2015 to 2016

- Created all programming for Immortal Beauty exhibition
- · Maintained a budget for all programming events
- Designed symposium materials (nametags, catalogs)
- Worked closely with curator to ensure programming ran smoothly and made all goals.

MANAGER IN TRAINING

Banana Republic - 2012 to 2015

- Implemented key visual themes throughout the store as head of visuals.
- Ensured that merchandise and store was easy to shop and accessible to customers
- Sold business and business casual garments for both male and female customers.

DRESS SPECIALIST

David's Bridal - 2011 to 2012

- Assisted in visual displays, merchandises, layouts, mannequin arrangement, and inventory management.
- · Provided quality customer service with sensitivity to individual requirements and special issues.
- Worked closely with management contributing ideas regarding dress coordination, accessories selection and wedding look.

EDUCATION

Masters of Science in Museum Leadership

DREXEL UNIVERSITY March 2016

Bachelor of Science in Textile and Fashion Design

UNIVERSITY OF WESTERN MICHIGAN

December 2009